Guide to the Carl and Shelley Smith Mydans Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1930-1992; Series I; 33.83; (106 boxes)
  - Slides
    - Housed in Slide Boxes
      - Philippine Elections -- Originals
        - Jaime Ongpin: Aquino bright supporter, Manila (two rolls): No. 1 - No. 2, 1986 January 30; (2 slide boxes) (Box 78)
        - President Marcos in his office at Malacanang Palace: No. 1 - No. 2 (1-2), 1986 January 31; (2 slide boxes) (Box 78)
        - Cory Aquino electioneering at Pasic Plaza outside of Manila near day's end. On platform talking with Neptali Gonzales, Assemblyman: No. 1 - No. 2(1-2), 1986 February 1; (2 slide boxes) (Box 78)
        - Boycott the Elections Rally made at post office building area, 1986 February 2 (Box 78)
        - Cory Aquino in her home in Manila as the elections near their end, 1986 February 3 (Box 78)
        - "Doy" Laurel at home as election nears end, 1986 February 5 (Box 78)
        - Marcos last rally on the Luneta: No. 1 - No. 2 (1-2), 1986 February 5; (2 slide boxes) (Box 78)
        - Cardinal Sin, press conference, Manila, 1986 February 5 (Box 78)
        - Arturo Tolentino at his home in Loyola Heights in Manila for Vice-President, 1986 February 6 (Box 78)
        - Marcos and daughters on mini-bus ride from Laoag to Batac, voting and with family -- including Ferdinand Jr. (only pictures of his son on this roll), also at elaborate home, Latac, 1986 February 7 (Box 78)
        - Seth, Luke, Carl and others, Philippines elections, 1986 January - February (Box 78)
        - Manila Hotel - outside and a local city hall in Manila (which one?), 1986 February (Box 78)
        - Marcos and family on his way in President's plane Fokker F-28 and daughters Irene and Imee (in red) on election day to vote at Batac (Imelda sees him off), 1986 February 7; (2 slide boxes) (Box 78)
        - Special Selects: Marcos and family, election day (15 frames), 1986 February 7 (Box 78)
        - At the Municipal Hall at Muntinlupa voters desperately guard voting boxes and count votes on the floor and on the outside grass, 1986 February 7 (Box 78)
        - Laurel speaking and Mrs. Aquino speaking at Santo Domingo Church; also daughter speaking, 1986 February 9 (Box 78)
        - Namfrel: Operation Quick Count; Manila, 1986 February (Box 78)
        - Bayan (New Peoples Alliance) rally at Plaza Miranda in front of Quiapo Church; fifty anti-Marcos, anti-American press: No. 1 - No. 2 (1-2), 1986 February 11; (2 slide boxes) (Box 78)
        - At the Binondo Church in Manila during the height of electioneering, Carita Calma and Reyando Toures are married, 1986 February 15 (Box 78)
        - Cory: at press conference -- first time not wearing yellow, 1986 February (Box 78)
        - Cory Aquino's last big rally on Lunetta: No. 1 - No. 3 (1-3), 1986 February 16; (3 slide boxes) (Box 78)
        - Aquino Spokesman Rene Saguisag, 1986 February (Box 78)
        - Rally at Post Office plaza called Liwasang Bonifacio, of the Bayan (left wing); some frames on the march to the p. office plaza at the American Embassy: No. 1 - No. 2 (1-2), 1986 February 18; (2 slide boxes) (Box 79)
        - Philippine Elections, special frames, originals, 1986 January - February (Box 79)
        - Marcos and Imelda in Honolulu (43 frames), 1986 April 16; (2 slide boxes) (Box 79)
        - Marcos and Sandra Burton in Honolulu, 1986 April 16 (Box 79)
        - Copy of Time pages with pictures by Carl Mydans, Philippines Elections, undated (Box 79)
        - Selection of 5 special frames -- originals --, undated (Box 79)
        - Philippines Elections: originals returned from "28 Days" book project, undated (Box 79)
      - Sunrise, Diamondhead, Honolulu, 1986 April 15 (Box 79)
      - Gloucester: Day-In-The-Life
        - Gloucester: Day-In-The-Life, 1986 May 2 (Box 79)
        - Over-alls, 1986 May 2; (2 slide boxes) (Box 79)
        - Gulls, 1986 May 2; (2 slide boxes) (Box 79)
        - The Angela and John Sanfilippo family at dinner, 1986 May 2 (Box 79)
          Includes negatives.
        - Street scenes, 1986 May 2 (Box 79)
        - Girl on the bow-sprit, 1986 May 2 (Box 79)
        - The Cemetery, 1986 May 2 (Box 79)
        - Fish dock scenes, 1986 May 2 (Box 79)
        - Dock and shipyards scenes, 1986 May 2 (Box 79)
        - Bakery, 1986 May 2 (Box 79)
        - The "They That Go Down-to-the-Sea" statue, 1986 May 2 (Box 79)
        - Annisquam Light, north side Cape Ann looking towards New Hampshire, 1986 May 2 (Box 79)
        - Eleven frames chosen to be kept by Day-In-The-Life (Dupes), 1986 May 2 (Box 79)
      - Recommissioning of the USS Missouri, San Francisco, 1986 May; (6 slide boxes) (Box 79)
      - Saratoga Opening, 1986 July; (12 slide boxes) (Box 79)
      - Hot air balloon aboard USS Intrepid, New York, 1986 July 4 (Box 79)
      - Lower New York Harbor from Brooklyn Heights, 1986 July 4 (Box 79)
      - Marcos and Imelda, Honolulu
        - With Seth, aides, and Filipino Consulate people, 1987 March 10 (Box 80)
        - No. 2 - No. 4, 1987 March 10; (4 slide boxes) (Box 80)
        - The House, 1987 March 10 (Box 80)
        - Dupes for Time, chosen by Julia Richer, 1987 March 10 (Box 80)
        - Frames (warm dupes) for Time, chosen by Julia Richer, 1987 March 10 (Box 80)
      - Block Island
        - Block Island and Point Judith, 1987 August (Box 80)
        - Block Island, 1987 August (Box 80)
        - Scenes: Block Island Light, 1987 August (Box 80)
        - The Rowans, Block Island, 1987 August (Box 80)
        - Joe Kastner, Block Island, 1987 August (Box 80)
      - Imelda Marcos at the Waldorf Towers, room 3724 suite on the 37th floor, 1988 November 1; (2 slide boxes) (Box 80)
      - United Nations
        - Kurt Waldheim, and others, scenes, 1977 November-December (Box 80)
        - UN Security Council, 1988 July 18; (3 slide boxes) (Box 80)
        - UN Secretary General Javier Perez de Cuellar at the UN, 1988 September 14 (Box 80)
        - United Nations Tests, Outside, 1988 November 30 (Box 80)
        - Jan Eliasson, Swedish Ambassador to the United Nations, in the Swedish Mission in New York, 1988 December 8 (Box 80)
        - Diego Cordovez, Ecuador Ambassador to the United Nations, 1988 December 9 (Box 80)
        - Giandomenico Picco, United Nations, 1991 December 6; (2 slide boxes) (Box 80)
      - Wall Pictures -- Palo Alto, California, 1989 April 2 (Box 80)
      - President Inauguration Day, 1989 (Box 80)
      - Tokyo, pictures made for NHK, 1989 December; (5 slide boxes) (Box 80)
      - National Geographic Seminar Slides, 1990 January 2; (6 slide boxes) (Box 80)
      - Sunsets: Choice of eight taken from this by Maryan Cornelly this morning for offer negs to advertisers, 1990 April 5 (Box 80)
      - Farm Security Administration, 1991, undated; (4 slide boxes) (Box 81)
      - Japanese Screen, 1991 March 26; (3 slide boxes) (Box 81)
      - Visa pour l'Image, Perpignan, France
        - Carl and Shelley Mydans by Douglas Kirkland, 1991 September 15 (Box 81)
        - Perpignan Photo Festival, 1991 September; (2 slide boxes) (Box 81)
      - Eddie Adams Workshop, 1991 and 1993; (6 slide boxes) (Box 81)
      - Pictorials for Printing. Offered Renee Mancini for syndication and not used., 1991 March (Box 81)
      - ICP Presentation, 1992 May 5; (4 slide boxes) (Box 81)
        Includes slides of Clark Field, SG Joe Smith, Carl and Shelley by Chinese, and extra set of slides for Palm Beach Photographic Centre Awards Ceremony.
      - Russia
        - Privatization of Russian Farms, 1992 October; (19 slide boxes) (Box 81)
        - Red Square with Arnold Drapkin, 1992 October (Box 81)
        - Moscow, Russia, Nina Stevens, 1992 October (Box 81)
      - Burma Dance
        - Nat dancer No. 1 - No. 3, (3 slide boxes) (Box 82)
        - Orchestra No. 1 - No. 2, (2 slide boxes) (Box 82)
        - Make-up rooms No. 1 - No. 2, (2 slide boxes) (Box 82)
        - Portraits No. 1 No. 2, (2 slide boxes) (Box 82)
        - Basic Beginner's Steps No. 1 - No. 2, (2 slide boxes) (Box 82)
        - Children's Classes (Box 82)
        - Teacher and dancer (Box 82)
        - Performance (Box 82)
        - Ramayana Scene (1st scene) (Box 82)
        - Bow Contest Dance from the Ramayana No. 1 - No. 2, (2 slide boxes) (Box 82)
        - Sorcerer dance also men dancers (Box 82)
        - Demon in Garden scene and Lover's Journey (Box 82)
        - Enchanted Deer Scene (Box 82)
        - Prime Selects No. 1 - No. 2, (2 slide boxes) (Box 82)
      - American Scene, J.F.K., undated (Box 82)
      - France -- Indochina, undated; (2 slide boxes) (Box 82)
      - Finland, undated (Box 82)
      - Italy, undated (Box 82)
      - Japan, undated; (3 slide boxes) (Box 82)
      - Singapore, undated (Box 82)
      - USA: Great Lakes Shipping, undated (Box 82)
      - Vietnam (Box 82)
      - Portraits
        Contains portraits and snapshots of people, including work for Blackstar.
        - 60 minutes (Television program)
          - During taping, 1979 January (Box 82)
          - Harry Reasoner, 1979 January; (2 slide boxes) (Box 82)
          - Senior Film Editor Kenneth Dalglish, 1979 February (Box 82)
          - Film Editor Joseph Murania, 1979 February (Box 82)
          - Carol Stein Film Editor, 1979 February (Box 82)
          - Film Editors; Carol Stein; Joseph Murania; Kenneth Dalglish (Senior) (available light), undated (Box 82)
          - Don Hewitt, 1979 February; (2 slide boxes) (Box 82)
          - Mike Wallace during taping, etc. also with Don Hewitt, undated (Box 82)
          - Mike Wallace (Koda 64) (Box 82)
          - Morley Safer, taping, 1979 February; (3 slide boxes) (Box 82)
          - Mike Wallace, Morley Safer, Harry Reasoner, Dan Rather, Don Hewitt (44 frames), 1980 January 7 (Box 83)
          - Dan Rather, 1979 February (Box 83)
          - Dan Rather: CBS Hostage Special "100 Days": No. 1 - No. 3 (1-3), 1980 February 11; (3 slide boxes) (Box 83)
          - Dan Rather: at his apartment, NYC: No. 1 and No. 2, 1980 February 12; (2 slide boxes) (Box 83)
          - Dan Rather: dupes of cover frame; also copies of cover in TIME, 1980 March (Box 83)
          - Dan Rather: CBS (blue), undated (Box 83)
          - Dan Rather, undated (Box 83)
          - Walter Cronkite, 1981 February 20-23; (3 slide boxes) (Box 83)
          - Ticker-tape Hostage Parade, New York City, New York, 1981 January 30 (Box 83)
        - Salvatore Accardo and the 1742 Paganini violin, 1982 November 5 (Box 83)
        - Paganini's own violin, the 1742 Guarnerius des Gesu, made in NYC, 1982 November 5 (Box 83)
        - Dr. Heinz Biesdorf. Cornell University. Money Magazine: No. 1 - No. 2 (1-2), 1980 June; (2 slide boxes) (Box 83)
        - Lester Bernstein, New York, 1979 June 22 (Box 83)
        - Ellen Boddie, unemployed, 1980 July 23; (2 slide boxes) (Box 83)
        - Reginald K. Brack, Jr. in his Time Inc. office, N.Y.C., 1986 December 23 (Box 83)
        - Ray Brady: CBS Commentator on business affairs, 1982 December 15 (Box 83)
        - Gov. Edmund G. Brown, Jr. campaigning in Maryland, 1976 May 5-6 (Box 83)
        - Artist Greg Brown paints Palo Alto with realistic scenes, 1977 April 20 (Box 83)
        - CBS
          - Andy Rooney, CBS Sixty Minutes, No. 1, 1980 May 12 (Box 83)
          - Thomas H. Wyman, CBS, 1980 June 12 (Box 83)
          - Van Gordon Sauter, President, CBS News, in his New York office, 1983 March 23 (Box 83)
          - Nigel Holmes at CBS, 1986 September 12 (Box 83)
          - Lawrence Tisch, day he moved into Wyman's office at CBS, 1986 September; (5 slide boxes) (Box 83)
        - Irwin S. Chanin in his office, 1982 December 30; (2 slide boxes) (Box 83)
        - Paul Charlap, Larchmont, 1979 October (Box 83)
        - Paul and Mary Anne Daley Charlap Wedding reception, Hommocks Road Larchmont, 1982 September 5 (Box 83)
        - Sir Winston Churchill, 1955 December 27 (Box 83)
        - Churchill at Syracusa, Italy [empty box], 1955 (Box 83)
        - Craig Claiborne with Pierre Franey, 1982 August; (3 slide boxes) (Box 83)
        - Dick Clurman, New York, 1989 August 3 (Box 83)
        - Dorothy Danner: World War Two Navy Nurse; POW in the Philippines, photographed at her home in Baton Rouge, 1991 February 25 (Box 83)
        - Sal DeMarco -- tests, one on camera, 1988 February (Box 84)
        - Alfred Eisenstaedt, 1979-1982; (2 slide boxes) (Box 84)
          Includes slides of Eisie with Carl Mydans.
        - Elizabeth II, Queen of Great Britain, and Sir Winston Churchill at the Garter Ceremony at Windsor Castle: No. 1 (1-2), 1956 June 18 (Box 84)
        - Carmine Ercolano, undated (Box 84)
        - Max Frankel, New York Times editor, 1986 October 20 (Box 84)
        - Diego Garcia, 1977 April; (3 slide boxes) (Box 84)
        - Arthur Gelb, New York Times, 1986 October 20 (Box 84)
        - Roberto Goizueta, Chairman of Coca Cola, NYC, 1985 April 25 (Box 84)
        - Sir James Goldsmith at his New York City house, 1987 November 2; (2 slide boxes) (Box 84)
        - Copy slides of pictures made of Jimmy Goldsmith elope story in Britain, No. 1 - No. 2, undated; (2 slide boxes) (Box 84)
        - Marcus Goodrich. Richmond, Va. (weeded), 1964 June 3 (Box 84)
        - Henry Grunwald in his office, 1987 March 24 (Box 84)
        - A.B. Guthrie, Jr., Missoula, Mont. (weeded), 1964 October 17 (Box 84)
        - Emily Hahn: NYC, 1981 September 3 (Box 84)
        - David Halberstam, at home, NYC, 1979 April 18 (Box 84)
        - Dirk Halstead, 1982 November 29 (Box 84)
        - Charles Hamilton, Autograph Specialist, New York, New York, 1983 April-May; (2 slide boxes) (Box 84)
        - Andrew Heiskell, being painted by Aaron Shikler in NYC, 1980 July 30 (Box 84)
        - Al Hirschfeld-Illustrator at Colonel Theatre, Boston, sketching "Foxfire", 1982 October 23 (Box 84)
        - Rudolph Hoglund, in his office, New York, Time, 1988-1989; (3 slide boxes) (Box 84)
        - Jack London Hosue, Valley of the Moon near Sonoma, California, 1985 July (Box 84)
        - Barbara Howar interviewing Patricia Neal for ABC's "Entertainment Tonight", 1983 May 5 (Box 84)
        - Gene Jankowski, President, CBS Broadcast, 1983 January 25; (2 slide boxes) (Box 84)
        - Kelly Johnson, Skunk Works, Lockheed, Burbank, California, 1977 December 19 (Box 84)
        - Joe Kaster, Larchmont, 1986 June 9 (Box 84)
        - William Kennedy, author, 1984 January 28 (Box 84)
        - Michael Kinsley, Editor at Harpers, 1983 May 5 (Box 84)
        - Kissinger with Vance and PRC Ambassador Hung Chen, 1977 January 8 (Box 84)
        - Henry Kissinger in his office at SEQUENCE, 1977 January 8; (2 slide boxes) (Box 84)
        - Henry and Nancy Kissinger at home with "Tyler" / Also with Jerry Schecter, undated (Box 84)
        - Jack Klugman and his "Jack's Crib" popcorn, No. 1 - No. 2, 1982 November 22; (2 slide boxes) (Box 84)
        - Ron Kriss in his office, 1989 February 10 (Box 84)
        - Chris Linen, Book of the Month Club Office, 1991 January 29 (Box 85)
        - Walter Lippmann, Washington, 1964 October 20 (Box 85)
        - Robert Longo, artist, New York City, New York, 1983 February 23; (2 slide boxes) (Box 85)
        - Stefan Lorant at home, Lenox, Massachusetts, No. 1 - No. 2, 1987 August 2; (2 slide boxes) (Box 85)
        - John D. MacDonald, Piseco, New York, 1979 September 23 (Box 85)
        - David McClintock, author, 1982 August 31 (Box 85)
        - Jim McKay (and Margaret McManus) on their farm in Maryland, 1983 December 27; (3 slide boxes) (Box 85)
        - Archbishop Makarious at the Geihinkan, Tokyo Press Conference, 1970 November 9 (Box 85)
        - Norris Church (Mrs. Norman Mailer), NYC, 1982 December 1 (Box 85)
        - Ralph Morse, 1982 November 29 (Box 85)
        - Noel Mostert: Singapore, 1974 December (Box 85)
        - George Nakashima
          - Daughter's House, 1972 July (Box 85)
          - Studio & Museum, 1972 July (Box 85)
          - Nakashima and Son Kevin, 1972 July (Box 85)
          - Nakashima Museum, 1972 July (Box 85)
          - Nakashima Workshops: No. 1 - No. 2, 1972 July; (2 slide boxes) (Box 85)
        - Herbert Padilla, Princeton, 1990 March 26 (Box 85)
        - Herbert Padilla, Princeton: No. 1 - No. 3, 1990 March 26; (3 slide boxes) (Box 85)
        - William Paley: CBS, 1970 February 16; (2 slide boxes) (Box 85)
        - Donald Reagan and Roger Birk of Merrill Lynch, 1980 July 16 (Box 85)
        - Kenneth Roland, head of Chemical Bank Equity Trading Section at the RCA Building, No. 2, 1982 August 27 (Box 85)
        - Jack Rosenthal, New York Times, 1986 October 20 (Box 85)
        - Roy Rowan at home, Byram, Connecticut, 1986 March 30; (3 slide boxes) (Box 85)
        - Richard Salant: NBC, 1979 September (Box 85)
        - Harrison Salisbury at home in Salisbury, 1985 September 13 (Box 85)
        - Dean Francis B. Sayer, Hugh Sidey and Washington National Cathedral, 1976 April 27 (Box 85)
        - Composer William Schuman, Greenwich, Connecticut, 1979 November 10 (Box 85)
        - Secretary of State, George P. Schultz at breakfast with Time Inc. Editors on 47th Floor, TL Building, 1986 October 1; (2 slide boxes) (Box 85)
        - William Seawell, PanAmerican, 1980 June 27 (Box 85)
        - Carl Mydans and William Shriver in Lenox, Massachusetts, 1989 November 21 (Box 85)
        - Muriel Spark: Rejects No. 1, New York (1-2) (weeded), 1964 October 15 (Box 86)
        - Patrick Steptoe, 1979 April 4 (Box 86)
        - Dr. Charles and Elizabeth Stroebel: New Haven, 1980 October 15; (4 slide boxes) (Box 86)
        - Time, Inc.
          - Time, Inc.: Don Burke, 1954 (Box 86)
          - Time Inc.: Test Color No. 2, Mibri Kessel and Grace McDermott in the Office, Bill Summits, 1958 February 6-7 (Box 86)
          - Time Inc., 1961 (Box 86)
          - Time Inc.: People, 1962 (Box 86)
          - Time Inc.: at Canaveral, 1962 (Box 86)
          - Time Inc., 1963 June 27 (Box 86)
          - Time Inc.: Tests around the Lab with "283", 1979 January 23 (Box 86)
          - Time Inc.: Al Freni, Ginny Halstead, Mary Ellen Simon, 1979 April 4 (Box 86)
          - Edward K. Thompson, 1985-1987; (6 slide boxes) (Box 86)
            Includes slides of Thompson at home in Mahopac, New York, and with granddaughter and great granddaughter.
          - Time Inc.: People, 1988 (Box 86)
          - Time photography people, 1990 Apr 7 (Box 86)
          - Presentation to Heiskell of Doris O'Neil's book of LIFE pictures, 1980 October 1 (Box 86)
        - Grant Tinker, Chairman of The Board, NBC, in his NY Office, 1983 January 4 (Box 86)
        - Judge Harold Tyler in his law offices at 30 Rockefeller Plaza, 1980 November 11 (Box 86)
        - Frederick Ungeheuer in Sir James Goldsmith's house in NYC, 1987 February 12 (Box 86)
        - Edgar Whitcomb, Larchmont, 1990 July 14 (Box 86)
        - Frank White, Hugh Patrick-Rusty Brown, 1982 July 9 (Box 86)
        - Teddy White: Bridgewater, Connecticut, 1978 April 15; (2 slide boxes) (Box 86)
        - Dakin Williams on his new book on Tennessee Williams in NYC, 1983 March 6-9; (2 slide boxes) (Box 86)
        - For "Asian business" W. R. A. Wyllie of Hutchinson International, undated; (2 slide boxes) (Box 86)
        - Lee Kuan Yew for Fortune, 1974 January (Box 86)
        - Pub Letter 1990 Summer Interns (Box 86)
        - Personalities, undated; (3 slide boxes) (Box 86)
        - Family and Friends
          - Helen Lambert's Moscow Paintings, 1961 (Box 86)
          - Sy Janow: sailing in Sugami Bay on his Chita II., 1971 February 7 (Box 86)
          - The John Riches: at Bates Island and also Portland, 1972 August (Box 86)
          - Franny and Doddie Mardulier and close-in scenes of nature, Cape Cod, 1972 August (Box 86)
          - Keyes, Yoko and Hannah Beech at Larchmont, 1977 August 7 (Box 86)
          - Doris O'Neil's New Milford, Connecticut home, 1977 August 9 (Box 86)
          - At the Goran and Christine Blome's Mamaroneck, 1983 December 29 (Box 86)
          - Stewart, Eisie (Alfred Eisenstaedt), Kessel, Duncan, Carl, Brown by Lane Stewart, 1985 March 22 (Box 86)
          - Misty and Claire at home, 1987 January 19 (Box 86)
          - Misty, Claire, Shelley, Yellow bear, Sacramento, California, 1988 May 5 (Box 86)
          - Claire, two years, 1988 May 7 (Box 87)
          - Eisie (Alfred Eisenstaedt): His office, 1991 October 1 (Box 87)
      - Animals
        - Horses, Wyoming, 1951 (Box 87)
        - Birds, Wildlife, Hommocks, 1962-1963 and 1972 (Box 87)
        - Pelicans and fish, Cape Canaveral, 1962 May (Box 87)
        - Birds, snakes, turtles, Texas, Greenwich, 1971 July (Box 87)
        - Orangutans, Sepilok (Borneo, Indonesia) and Surabaya Zoo (Surabaya, Indonesia), 1973 March; (12 slide boxes) (Box 87)
        - Bali Zoo, Surabaya, Indonesia, 1973 July-August (Box 87)
        - Bates Island, Maine, Birds and things along the shore, 1972 August (Box 87)
        - Leatherback Turtles, Terengganu, Malaysia, 1974 June; (17 slide boxes) (Box 87)
        - Birds and Bird Watchers, 1977; (4 slide boxes) (Box 87)
          Includes slides from Palo Alto and Santa Cruz, California and Hommocks, New York.
        - Gulls: second shooting, 1977 December 23 (Box 87)
        - Gulls: Eastman Kodak Colorama Grand Central Station, 1978 March-April; (2 slide boxes) (Box 87)
        - Birds: Canada Geese, Larchmont, 1978 July 9 (Box 87)
        - Canada Geese, Larchmont, 1979 June (Box 87)
        - Spiders, Larchmont, 1979 September (Box 87)
        - Gulls: San Francisco, 1979 October (Box 88)
        - Hommocks Road: Nature, 1979 November (Box 88)
        - Nesting, sitting Pheasant at Barnes, Larchmont, 1980 May 17 (Box 88)
        - Swans, Mamaroneck, New York, 1980 May-July; (6 slide boxes) (Box 88)
        - For Discover: Peregrine Falcon's next box in NYC, 1980 July (Box 88)
        - Animals: Raccoons at Ed and Lee Thompson, 1981 September (Box 88)
        - Swans: Mamaroneck, New York, 1980 July (Box 88)
        - Swans: Hommocks Road, 1982 July 4 (Box 88)
        - Winter birds, Hommocks Road, Larchmont, New York, 1988 January (Box 88)
        - Larchmont Winter scene, 1988 January (Box 88)
        - Hommocks Road Scenes: Our house, swans, Grechen Point house, orphans of the storm, firemen at Zeeman house, Joyce Miralia with Louise and Kenneth and Shelley and dogs, 1988 May-June (Box 88)
        - Hommocks and environment, tests with Kodachrome 200 and Nikkor 180 f2.8 with two time ext. becomes 360 mm lens at 5.6, swans, gulls, storks, harbor scenes, 1988 June (Box 88)
        - Jurong Bird Park, Singapore, undated; (8 slide boxes) (Box 88)
        - Sea Gulls, undated (Box 88)
      - Other Slides
        - Early years, undated; (2 slide boxes) (Box 88)
        - Betel Nut, undated (Box 88)
        - Hunger: Santo Tomas, Receipt Writing, undated (Box 88)
        - Old Age: Hands, undated (Box 88)
        - Special color selection -- Maryann Kornely, undated (Box 88)
        - Old printed transparencies of various periods, undated (Box 88)
        - FE on automatic with 28 mm lens and no corrective filter; Time Inc scenes and people, 1978 July (Box 88)
        - FE Automatic with Ekt 200 and 28 mm lens and fluorescent filter, Time Inc: Scenes and people, 1978 July 24 (Box 88)
        - Time Inc: Tests of new 85 mm lens at F-2, 1979 June (Box 88)
        - Time Inc: Tests for new 20 mm 3.5 lens, 1979 June 13 (Box 88)
        - Retrospective: slides for China section, undated; (10 slide boxes) (Box 88)
        - SUN: 500 mm Singapore, 1973 July (Box 89)
        - Dupes of 7 Frames of Soviet Missiles being shipping [sic] back to USSR from Cuba, undated (Box 89)
        - Hommocks Road, Larchmont, tests and Time Inc. photographers gathering, 1982 July-August; (2 slide boxes) (Box 89)